

1 (123) 456 78 99

Alabama

www.qwikresume.com

Professional Summary

A Civil Engineer with 4 years of experience in construction and infrastructure projects like chicken farm, warehouses, residential buildings, villas and water channels. Experienced in site supervision, construction works, accountancy, tendering and evaluation. Experience in prestressing detailed drawings. Knowledge of construction methods and construction sequences in civil structural constructions above or below the ground.

Work Experience

Civil Engineer

ABC Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Los Angeles, CA

- Evaluate subdivision, cluster, and other application requests from the Department of Planning and Permitting with respect to availability of water, past commitments, and facility requirements.
- Does manual calculations to determine fire flows and system pressures.
- Uses hydraulic models to calculate system flows and pressures.

Civil Engineer

ABC Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Los Angeles, CA

- Delivery of mining samples from tipple to Assay Department.
- Remove trash, residual building debris and potential dangerous materials from milling sites.
- · Worked in the payroll section as timekeeper.

Education

M.S. in structural engineering

University of Hawaii at Manoa Jan / 2019 - Ongoing New York

Skills Microsoft Office GIS SAP2000 StruCalc

Achievements

Award